weddingmapper.com 2019-04-29

# Wedding Mapper

**Privacy Policy**

Last Updated: June 18th, 2010

**SUMMARY**

We take the privacy of our users very seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about how we treat personally identifiable information. We provide this Privacy Policy because you have a right to know what information we collect, how it is protected and used, and the circumstances under which it may be disclosed. If you have comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [[email protected]](https://www.weddingmapper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#bfcfcdd6c9dedcc6ffe8dadbdbd6d1d8f2decfcfdacd91dcd0d2) or in writing at: Privacy Director, Community Walk, 880 Lombard Street, San Francisco, CA 94133. 

**Online Privacy Standards.** While there are no official standards governing privacy practices on the Internet, we look to the principles supported by the Federal Trade Commission's Fair Information Practices Principles for guidance, currently available at http://www.ftc.gov/reports/privacy3/tos.htm. 

**What This Policy Covers.** This policy covers Wedding Mapper's treatment of personally identifiable information that we obtain when you visit our website or use our services. We regard personally identifiable information as information that someone can use to identify or contact you in person, such as real name, telephone number, birth date, email address, or physical mailing address. Information that we use internally to identify you as a user in our system, such as your selected username and password, is not considered personally identifiable information.

**What This Policy Does Not Cover.** This policy does not cover the privacy practices of third parties that we do not own or control, such as any partners or advertisers. In addition, we may provide links to other services and on occasion to other sites that may interest you. All of these sites operate independently of Wedding Mapper and they may have their own privacy or security practices. We encourage you to review their policies before submitting any personal information to them.

**1\. HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION**

**A Information You Provide**

**Registration Information.** During the registration process, we collect your first and last name and email address. We will send you an email to verify that you are the owner of this address. You will also choose a username and password that we will use to identify you in our system.

**Optional User Profile Information.** In the future, we may include optional user profile information. If we provide that as part of the service, you will be able to choose to provide us with additional optional information about yourself (for example, your name, address, age, etc.), which helps us deliver a more personalized experience to you. This information may be made available in your publicly available user profile page. 

**Access To Your Personal Information.** In general, we make it easy for you to view your personally identifiable information in your user profile page, where you can add, edit, or delete it as you see fit. You can access your user profile page by logging in at this link: [http://www.WeddingMapper.com](http://www.weddingmapper.com/) and clicking on "User Information."

**Third Party Advertising Networks.** Some of the advertisements that appear on the WeddingMapper.com web site are delivered to you by national internet advertising and application company such as Adify. This company utilizes certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to our site(s), including information about the banner ads they display, and cookie they place on your computer and your IP address. To opt out of information collection by Adify, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policy, please visit their website at: http://www.adify.com/adify-opt-out-program http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**B. Information We Do Not Collect**

**Children.** As explained further in our Terms of Service, available at www.WeddingMapper.com/company/policies/terms_of_service, our website is intended for adults only. You must be 13 years of age or older to register to use our website. Therefore, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information about children. If you believe that we have information from or about anyone under 13 years of age, please notify us by email at [[email protected]](https://www.weddingmapper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or write to our Privacy Director at the address noted above.

**Social Security Number.** We do not ask for or require your social security number to use any part of the Services or to access any part of our site.

**C. Information We Track**

**Log Files.** Similar to many websites, we gather certain anonymous, non-personal information automatically and store it in web server log files. This information includes Internet protocol addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), site entry/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to improve our site, analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements around the site, and gather aggregate information about our user base as a whole. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or users from which individual user identities have been removed, and therefore does not include your personally identifiable information.

**Cookies.** As you browse the Wedding Mapper site, cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive. A cookie is a small text file that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. It can also help us understand how our site visitors click to our site, and what pages they view during their visit. Similar to many websites, we store an encrypted cookie on your computer so we can remember you when you come back to our website without requiring you to log-in every time. Cookies also allow us to track and understand the interests of our users to enhance the overall experience on our site. 

You can set your web browser software to disable cookies. To do so, please refer to the help section of your specific browser for more information on how to manage or disable cookies. If you disable cookies, you may still view our site, but some areas of our site will not work properly.

Some of our business partners, such as advertisers, may also use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies, and, as noted above, this privacy policy does not govern the use of cookies by our business partners or advertisers.

**2\. HOW WE USE INFORMATION**

**Communication of Service-related Announcements.** We use emails and/or prominent notifications on our website as our primary means to inform our users of service-related announcements from Wedding Mapper. We may use your email address to deliver important service-related announcements. Example service-related announcements include: email verification during registration, requests for a password reset, important security or server maintenance updates, software updates, upgrades, and new releases, or policy changes. These service-related announcements are considered a fundamental part of our service, and users cannot opt-out of these email announcements.

**On Our Website.** We may use information provided by you on our website in the following ways:

  * **Identification Of Authors By Username.** We are web-based service that allows users to create annotated Google Maps by adding location markers and route markers to a map that is saved in a specific state. Users can upload images, display content from other sites, leave comments, and get directions on your maps through our service. In providing this service, we depend in part on the contributions and actions of our users to improve the quality of the experience users have with the service. When you make a contribution to Wedding Mapper (such as adding a comment, modifying someone else's comment or content, you will be identified by your username as the author of that contribution. In any of these circumstances, we will only identify you by your username.

  * **In Your Public User Profile.** If we provide a public user profile page in the future, you will have the option to include your personally identifiable information in your public user profile, but you are not required to do so. You can easily add, edit, and delete information in your public user profile through the user profile page.

  * **For Site Statistics.** As noted above, we use information collected from our web log files to calculate and publish anonymous, non-personal, aggregate statistics that we believe our users are interested in viewing. For example, we track and publish the total number of users who have viewed a particular web page. We publish this data in aggregate form only, and do not tie it to any personally identifiable information.

**For Internal Reporting and Internal Analysis.** As noted above, we use information gathered from log files and cookies to improve our site, analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements around the site, and to gather aggregate information about our user base as a whole. We do not tie this data to personally identifiable information.

**3\. HOW WE DISCLOSE INFORMATION**

**On Our Website.** We may choose to provide a group blog or message board in the future. These features would allow you to communicate with other users by posting public messages. Please be aware that what you write in these public messages can be viewed, collected or used by anyone who visits our website. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you submit or permit others to submit through public messages.

**Sharing, Renting, and Selling Information We Collect With Third-Parties.** Except as described in this section, we will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties without notifying you of our intent to share the information and giving you an opportunity to prevent your information from being shared. We occasionally use other companies, agents or contractors to perform services necessary to our operations. For example, we have partnered with other companies to develop our website, personalize our web pages and analyze users' interaction with our site. By contractual agreement, these companies must treat your information in accordance with this privacy policy. We will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies. In addition, we share anonymous, non-personal, aggregate information about our user base with partners or advertisers, and, as mentioned above, we may publish these aggregate usage statistics on our website for the interest of our users. We do not tie this shared or published data to personally identifiable information. 

**As Necessary In Legal Circumstances.** We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

**As Necessary In An Acquisition.** If our company is acquired, all of our assets, including user information, may be transferred to the acquiring company. At that time, your user information may become subject to the acquiring company's privacy policy. Before we transfer your user information, we will notify you either by email or by posting a notice on our site.

**4\. HOW WE KEEP INFORMATION SECURE**

**Security of User Profile Information.** Your user profile information is password-protected. We will not share your password with anyone. Please do not share your password with anyone, and remember to change your password from time to time, to keep your user information secure.

**Network Security.** We have implemented a variety of commercially standard encryption and security technologies and procedures to protect information, including your personal information, stored in our computer systems from unauthorized access. Please be aware that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, thus we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, but we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Management Procedures.** We also maintain standard physical and electronic procedural safeguards that limit access to your personally identifiable information to our employees (or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) who, through the course of standard business activities, need to access your personally identifiable information.

**5\. YOUR PERSONAL CHOICES**

**Information With Other Users.** If we provide a public user profile page in the future, you will be able to control what personal information about you is shared with other users in your public user profile, and what information you choose to keep private. You can view, add, edit, and delete information in your public user profile through your user profile page.

**Editing and Deleting User Profile Information.** You can view the personally identifiable information we have collected from you in your user profile page where you can add, edit, or delete it as you see fit. You may also request deletion of your user account through your user profile page.

**6\. UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

From time to time, we will review and make changes to our privacy policy. When we do so, we will either notify you by email or place a notice on our website. Users should check back for updates to this policy. The most recent version of our privacy policy is always available from a link on our homepage, and at [www.WeddingMapper.com/company/policies/privacy](http://www.weddingmapper.com/company/policies/privacy).

**7\. YOUR CONSENT TO THIS POLICY**

By using the Wedding Mapper website, you agree to this privacy policy. This is our entire and exclusive privacy policy and it supercedes any earlier version. Our Terms of Service take precedence over any conflicting privacy policy provision.

**8\. LEGAL DISCLAIMER**

The Wedding Mapper website operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond our control. This privacy policy is governed by California law, excluding conflicts of law principles.
